<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>swaatom.com</title>
    <link>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on swaatom.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 17:30:00 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cabin fever</title>
      <link>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/posts/cabin-fever/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 17:30:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/posts/cabin-fever/</guid>
      <description>Here I am, stuck inside four walls in my room in Ta Khmau. There&amp;rsquo;s no official lockdown here, but it makes sense to limit social contact. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna escape for a while tomorrow though, and head across the river to visit the family. I think that I&amp;rsquo;m pretty well socially distanced riding a bicycle. I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to it. I&amp;rsquo;m in two minds whether to take the ferry though (very crowded), or ride all the way up to the Prek Tamak bridge and back south again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skanked by the bank</title>
      <link>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/posts/skanked-by-the-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/posts/skanked-by-the-bank/</guid>
      <description>Occasionally, something happens that brings out my inner Victor Meldrew. In this case, I think it was justified. I&amp;rsquo;ve had an account with ABA bank since I moved to Cambodia five years ago. This morning, the school contacted me to say that they couldn&amp;rsquo;t transfer my wages to my account. How very odd. So I got on the app, and saw that my account was in credit, everything okay - but hold on a minute, what&amp;rsquo;s this?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School&#39;s out</title>
      <link>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/posts/schools-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 11:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/posts/schools-out/</guid>
      <description>This time is different. I think that Cambodia&amp;rsquo;s amazing run of good luck has come to an end. The virus is with us now, and this time it appears to be here to stay. The genie ain&amp;rsquo;t gonna go back in the bottle this time. I hope I&amp;rsquo;m wrong. I would love to be wrong. It could&amp;rsquo;ve all been prevented. When will life return to normal? Ellen had only just started school when all of the covid closures kicked in last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up the blog</title>
      <link>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/posts/setting-up-the-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/posts/setting-up-the-blog/</guid>
      <description>My first project is simply this blog. I have to:-
 Create some minimal content and pages Choose and apply a theme Create a repository on github Publish on github pages Set the nameservers for the swaatom.com domain to point to this blog  When I succeed, you will be able to read this blog!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world!</title>
      <link>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/posts/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 12:49:11 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/posts/hello/</guid>
      <description>Welcome!
I&amp;rsquo;m writing here because I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to return to coding. Coding has missed me (LOL).
I started messing around with code in 1982, using a Sinclair ZX81. After uni, I worked as a software / web developer for six years. So I&amp;rsquo;ve been around for quite some time. After a while I reached a phase in my life when I never wanted to look at a screen ever again. Splitting headaches, RSI, the works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10,000 kilometres</title>
      <link>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/posts/10000km/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 06:30:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/posts/10000km/</guid>
      <description>Cycling has to be one of the best things that anybody can do. Transport, exercise and stress relief all combined in one easy package. I took a short break on my commute into Phnom Penh to capture this moment. Me and my trusty Giant bicycle were about to mark a metric milestone together.
 My bicycle: Giant Rincon Disc
 Check out the odometer reading: 9,999 kilometres. That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of riding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my website’s about page. It’s been a long time, and it’s about time I started putting stuff out there on the old interweb again.  This site is intended as nothing more than a blog to document life, the universe, and everything. I built it primarily for my own benefit, and to share my experiences and eminent sagacity with my fellow simians. I hope it can be of some use or value to all who stumble across it, but make no claims that it will be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cambodia</title>
      <link>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/cambodia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/cambodia/</guid>
      <description>  Cambodia, the kingdom of wonder
 Hi there!  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun</title>
      <link>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/fun/</guid>
      <description>Everyone needs to have some fun. Especially now, with all the doom and gloom that seems omni-present at the moment.  I&#39;m going to use this page to link to posts that I have categorised as &#34;fun&#34;. At the moment, that includes things like family time, cycling, reading good books, boats and whatever takes my fancy at any given moment. Sadly, scuba diving won&#39;t feature here because I haven&#39;t been in the water for over ten years now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life</title>
      <link>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/life/</guid>
      <description>Life. Don&#39;t talk to me about life...
Okay, I&#39;m not Marvin the paranoid android. Life actually is worth talking about sometimes. It can be beautiful and colourful. There are lots of things we can share and do. Sometimes we get so wrapped up in all the sh1t going on around us, it is easy to forget to take time out to do things with friends and family. I&#39;m going to use this blog to remind myself where my priorities lie and what my motivations are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://swaatomdotcom.github.io/swaatom-blog/projects/</guid>
      <description> I hope to do some projects soon.
(the first project is getting this website hosted on github pages)  {% for post in site.categories.projects %} {{post.title}} {% endfor %}  -- </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>